[
  {
    "id":0,
    "name":"Learn Persian",
    "cards":[
      {
        "id":0,
        "front":"سلام | Salam",
        "back":"Hi | Hello"
      },
      {
        "id":1,
        "front":"قدرت | Qodrat",
        "back":"Power"
      },
      {
        "id":2,
        "front":"میمون | Maymoon",
        "back":"Monkey"
      },
      {
        "id":3,
        "front":"کشتن | Koshtan",
        "back":"To kill"
      },
      {
        "id":4,
        "front":"برنامه | Bar name",
        "back":"Plan | Program"
      },
      {
        "id":5,
        "front":"مرگ | Marg",
        "back":"Death"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "id":0,
    "name":"Famous People",
    "cards":[
      {
        "id":0,
        "front":"ولین زن برنده مدال فیلدز ؟",
        "back":"مریم میرضا خانی"
      },
      {
        "id":1,
        "front":"سازنده پی پال | اسپیس ایکس | تسلا ؟",
        "back":"ایلان ماسک"
      },
      {
        "id":2,
        "front":"خالق سیستم عامل لینوکس ؟",
        "back":"لینوس توروالدز"
      },
      {
        "id":3,
        "front":"کشتن | Koshtan",
        "back":"To kill"
      }
    ]
  }
]
